verychic.com 2014-11-22

# VeryChic - Exceptional hotels. Exclusive offers - Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy for the website www.VeryChic.com

1\. Introduction

VeryChic SAS, an online travel agency that operates by means of a website, available at the following address: [www.verychic.com](http://www.verychic.com/). By using the VeryChic site and its services, you agree to accept the Terms and Conditions and terms of the Privacy Policy. We invite you to read this charter that sets out the use of data that is collected on our site.

2\. Changing of the Privacy Policy

VeryChic reserves the right to change and edit the content of the Privacy Policy at any time. The company will do its best to communicate and notify you to any changes to conditions, through this page.

3\. Use of data

We are committed to only using data collected, for the following purposes:  
\- Verifying your identity  
\- Send information about our products and services  
\- Successfully executing bookings  
\- Confirmation of your reservation with the hotel, via the sending of your booking request  
\- Debiting the deposit corresponding to your booking  
\- Collecting your opinions and impressions about our products and our services  

4\. Information sharing

Sharing of your information will occur strictly in the following situations, no other situation will justify the distribution of your data without your personal agreement:  
\- In the event of a full or partial sale of our business, or of restructuring or substantial reorganization of the company. At such times, we may be called upon to transmit data to third parties, but in all cases we will make sure to protect your personal data.  
\- As part of a legal requirement, such as a court order, or for preventions of fraud and other crimes.  

5\. Information automatically collected from your computer

Upon connecting to our website, our web server collects your internet (IP) address: This does not identify you and is not linked to your personal data. It helps only to facilitate the management of our site.  
Certain non-personal data, such as what web browser is used, can be collected in certain cases to allow us to provide a more efficient service.  

6\. Cookies

Cookies, containing certain information concerning you, may be stored on your computer when you browse our website. This information is sometimes used to track and to store data, but they are limited to the server: we can under no circumstance track your web browsing. Your credit card details will never be stored in cookies. Cookies are used to improve navigation on the site and provide you with a higher quality, personalised service. They allow, among other things, to avoid continually re-entering your information each time you visit our site or for us to better understand how our site is used and consulted. If you wish, you can delete cookies from your computer, although doing so could result in a malfunction of the site.  

7\. Changing your data

You retain the right to modify your personal information at any time, by accessing "My Account". You can also contact us by recorded delivery mail to the following address: VeryChic, 23, rue d'Anjou, 75008 Paris, France.  

8\. Security

The data that is shared either automatically or that you enter, including your bank details when making a purchase, are secured by the security systems put in place on our site to avoid misuse or unauthorized access: the SSL cryptographic protocol ensures the encryption of your banking information prior to its transmission.  

9\. Hyperlinks to third party websites

When being redirected to a third party site via hyperlinks present on our own site, we are in no way responsible for the practices performed and dictated by the Privacy Policies of said sites. We urge you to review the privacy policies of all the sites you visit and contact the specialist advisers from those same companies if you have concerns. By the same token, if you are redirected to our site via a link contained on a page from third party sites, we are again not responsible for the practices employed by the privacy policy of those sites.  

10\. Contact us

For more information about our Privacy Policy, Security or the sharing your personal information, you can contact us by telephone on +442033265476 from the UK, +3228087125 from Belgium, +41215750002 from Switzerland, +46840308780 from Sweden, +34911366109 from Spain, +496994189328 from Germany, +31202623731 from the Netherlands, +390689970066 from Italy, +4578791033 from Denmark, +4312675948 from Austria, +4721999483 from Norway, +33170958585 from France (additional call charges may apply), or by email at [contact@verychic.com](mailto:contact@verychic.com) or by post at 23 rue d'Anjou - 75008 Paris - France.  

11\. Declaration to the CNIL

In order to protect your data and comply with data protection law, VeryChic has made a declaration to the French supervisory authority, ** ** the CNIL, under registration number No. 1529746. In any situation, pursuant to Article 32 of the Data Protection Act of 6 January 1978 amended by Law 2004-801 of August 6, 2004 and the order of August 24, 2011, you have a right to access, modify, rectify and delete personal data concerning you. You may exercise that right at any time by sending an email to contact@verychic.com address or by writing to VeryChic SAS at 23, rue d'Anjou - 75008 - Paris, France, subject to proof of identity.  

12\. Unsubscribe from our newsletters

If you no longer wish to receive emails from VeryChic, please visit this page:  
<http://www.vrcfb.net/unsubscribe/index-v2.php?lang=en>

If you have an account on VeryChic, you should access this page via the unsubscribe link located at the bottom of emails we send you.
